

Associate L2 | ETL Tester

raval.mrudul78@gmail.com 9924444066

Experienced Software Tester with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in MSSQL, Selenium WebDriver,ETL and Strong quality assurance professional with a Master of Computer Applications (MCA) focused in Computer Science from Shrimad Rajchandra Institute of Management and Computer Application (SRIMCA).

Key Skills

Test Planning
Manual Testing
Test Case Drafting
Test Scenario Drafting
Selenium Automation Testing
Jmeter and API Testing
MS SQL
ETL
Robotic Automation Process

Professional Experience

February 2022 -Present

QA Analyst

1Rivet, Valsad, Gujarat, India

- Designed progress reports including statistics on completion rate, defects, fixes, etc.
- Designed Test plans, Test scenarios, Test Queries based on Mapping Documnets and Business
- · Developed and executed test plans, test objectives, and test cases.
- · Regression testing, Backend testing, Acceptance Testing UAT.
- Disccusion with Clients Regarding Data Analysis and Requirements

May 2020 -February 2022 Software Quality Assurance Team Lead

Toshal Infotech, Surat Area, India

- Allocation of work and Test case review.
- Conduct daily scrums, Retrosepctices and Grooming meetings.
- Coordinate and support during production outages.
- Coordinate with Team members for smooth project execution.
- · Defect analysis, reporting and tracking on daily basis.
- · Design of scenarios and test cases.
- Defect analysis, reporting and tracking on daily basis.
- Design of test cases after reviewing User stories.
- Interact with the Client and getting the requirements that need to be tested.
- · Perform smoke, server patches testing.
- Performed testing in Production and Component Test environments.
- Prepare Test Strategy and planning documents.
- User stories analysis, understanding scope, and acceptance criteria.

September 2015 -December 2019 Software Tester

Toshal Infotech, Surat, Gujarat, India

- Designed progress reports including statistics on completion rate, defects, fixes, etc.
- Designed Test plans, Test scenarios and Test cases based on business objectives and project artifacts.
- Developed and executed test plans, test objectives, and test cases.
- Executed System testing, System Integration SIT, Functional testing, Regression testing, Backend testing, Cross-browser testing and User Acceptance Testing UAT.
- Make sure that test cases and test strategy cover every aspect to catch defects at initial stages
 of testing.
- Performed System Integration testing, Functional testing, Regression testing, Database, Exploratory testing and User Acceptance Testing for a web application.
- Worked with a development team to understand technical design and architecture.

Education

February 2014

Master of Computer Applications (MCA) in Computer Application Shrimad Rajchandra Institute of Management and Computer Application (SRIMCA)

March 2011

Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) in Computer Application College of Applied Sciences & Professional Studies at Chikhli

Accomplishments

Paper Published

Sheth J.,Naik N.,Raval M.,â \in Comparative study of Spelling Checking

Algorithm for Gujarati Languages†Vol 4, No.2

Course Completed

- Agile BM 101 Introduction to Agile Business Management
- Agile Fundamentals: Including Scrum and Kanban 2022
- Azure DevOps Boards for Project Managers/Analyst/Developers
- Build complex XPath locators for Selenium automation that will work on any web element
- Data Warehouse ETL Testing & Data Quality Management A-Z
- Machine Learning for Absolute Beginners Level 1
- MySQL, SQL and Stored Procedures from Beginner to Advanced
- Selenium WebDriver with Java and TestNG. Tutorial designed for complete beginners in Selenium testing and automation
- WebDriverIO + Node.js -JavaScript UI Automation from Scratch